Vigor Arisandi



vigorarisandi94@gmail.com



inkedin.com/in/vigorarisandi

An unorthodox UI/UX designer with strong business backgrounds. Specialized in semantic structure, system flow design, design system, as well as conveying information. An MBA graduate who focused in social commerce, cross-cultural communication, and data analysis.

RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer | Funpodium

January 2020 - Present (+3y)

- Built a design library from scratch for 6 PaaS modules
- Designed and maintained 423 and 434 pages of mockups in 2020 and 2021
- Made PRDs based on qualitative research and usability tests for 3 module packages
- Created product roadmaps for 4 PaaS module packages

UX Assistant | Funpodium

March 2019 - January 2020 (11m)

- Conducted data analysis from an analytics service for the 3 core functions
- Created data tracking plans to uncover <u>+</u>20% additional business insights
- Produced wireframes and mockups for iOS and Android screens

EDUCATION

Nielsen Norman Group | Virtual UX Conference

September 2020. Online.

Designing Complex Apps for Specialized Domains: Score of 97%

Information Architecture: Score of 93%

National Sun Yat-sen University

September 2016 - September 2018. Kaohsiung, Taiwan.

MBA in International Business GPA of 4.0

TOOLS

Figma

Zeplin

Sketch

Notion

Keynote

Ms Excel

Whimsical

Confluence

Power Point